<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mysoft LLC</title>
	<atom:link href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/mep_org/mysoft-llc/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 07:50:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/favicon-32x32-1.png</url>
	<title>Mysoft LLC</title>
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Music Melodious &#8211; Shreya Ghoshal &#8211; Mumbai 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/music-melodious-shreya-ghoshal-mumbai-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 06:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience the melodious voice of Shreya Ghoshal by booking your tickets for her upcoming live shows. With the convenience of buying online tickets and a list of upcoming event dates available, you can easily plan your attendance to fit your schedule. Don’t miss out on the chance to see Shreya Ghoshal perform her greatest hits &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/music-melodious-shreya-ghoshal-mumbai-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Music Melodious &#8211; Shreya Ghoshal &#8211; Mumbai 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the melodious voice of Shreya Ghoshal by booking your tickets for her upcoming live shows. With the convenience of buying online tickets and a list of upcoming event dates available, you can easily plan your attendance to fit your schedule. Don’t miss out on the chance to see Shreya Ghoshal perform her greatest hits and new material live on stage.</p>
<p>Shreya Ghoshal is indian playback singer. She is alos performed so many live show and concerts. She was seen by Sanjay Leela Bhansali when she won the musical Sa Re Ga Ma Pa at the sixteen years old.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Zakir Khan Show &#8211; Pune  2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Zakir Khan is one of the the brightest comedians in the country, as proven by the massive success of his recent Haq Se Single tour, and the Amazon Prime special of the same name. Zakir created waves in 2016 with his appearance on AIB Diwas, as he swiftly went on to become what AIB founder &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023-2/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The Zakir Khan Show &#8211; Pune  2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zakir Khan is one of the the brightest comedians in the country, as proven by the massive success of his recent Haq Se Single tour, and the Amazon Prime special of the same name. Zakir created waves in 2016 with his appearance on AIB Diwas, as he swiftly went on to become what AIB founder Tanmay Bhat described as “The biggest stand-up comedy act in India. Period”.</p>
<p>A writer by profession, this &#8216;Confused Desi&#8217; serves his take on modern India, with a hard-to-resist style of humour that&#8217;ll have you nodding your heads and clapping as you relate to everything he says.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holi Hai &#124; The Land of Colours @ Aqua Pune</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/holi-hai-the-land-of-colours-aqua-pune/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Get ready for the Most ‘Splashtastic Holi Bash in Pune’! Get drenched in fun &#38; excitement at Wet N Joy Splas. This Holi, Splash water in the “India’s Biggest Wave Pool Party” and get High on Non-stop Music. Get access to unlimited Rides, Wavepool, Rain Dance, Meals, Thandai &#38; Fun all day.. Enjoy 25 International &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/holi-hai-the-land-of-colours-aqua-pune/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Holi Hai &#124; The Land of Colours @ Aqua Pune</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Get ready for the Most ‘Splashtastic Holi Bash in Pune’! Get drenched in fun &amp; excitement at Wet N Joy Splas.</p>
<p>This Holi, Splash water in the “India’s Biggest Wave Pool Party” and get High on Non-stop Music. Get access to unlimited Rides, Wavepool, Rain Dance, Meals, Thandai &amp; Fun all day.. Enjoy 25 International Rides and Activities brought from North America &amp; Canada</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lock The Box &#8211; Bookfair Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/lock-the-box-bookfair-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17228</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As the second wave of pandemic nears its end, Lock the box &#8211; Bookfairs will not be the same anymore. It will have to have the added practices we have learnt to cope in the abnormal situations. Book fairs need to address requirements of the new normal. Concerns such as social distancing, wearing of masks, &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/lock-the-box-bookfair-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Lock The Box &#8211; Bookfair Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the second wave of pandemic nears its end, Lock the box &#8211; Bookfairs will not be the same anymore. It will have to have the added practices we have learnt to cope in the abnormal situations. Book fairs need to address requirements of the new normal. Concerns such as social distancing, wearing of masks, vaccination etc. will all be part of the new normal.</p>
<p>“In the new age of book fairs, the online and /or hybrid models will be tried by various organizers from time to time. The event will be fine-tuned to suit requirements of one and all. We at Pune Bookfair will ensure that the modern day practices and the requirements of the new normal will be incorporated in our exhibitions, conferences and meets (offline) so as to benefit one and all.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
