<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Party</title>
	<atom:link href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/mep_cat/party/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 07:49:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/favicon-32x32-1.png</url>
	<title>Party</title>
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Raas Dandiya Fever &#124; Dandiya Nights &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/raas-dandiya-fever-dandiya-nights-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enchanting Rhythms: Dandiya Fever Festival is an exuberant and vibrant celebration of traditional Indian culture, specifically centered around the traditional folk dance form of Dandiya Raas. Colorful Costumes encouraged participants to wear in the event. DJ Music and Performances: Dandiya music, creating an energetic atmosphere that will keep participants dancing. Professional performers may also grace &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/raas-dandiya-fever-dandiya-nights-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Raas Dandiya Fever &#124; Dandiya Nights &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enchanting Rhythms: Dandiya Fever Festival is an exuberant and vibrant celebration of traditional Indian culture, specifically centered around the traditional folk dance form of Dandiya Raas.</p>
<ul>
<li>Colorful Costumes encouraged participants to wear in the event.</li>
<li>DJ Music and Performances: Dandiya music, creating an energetic atmosphere that will keep participants dancing. Professional performers may also grace the stage with captivating dance routines, showcasing the beauty and diversity of Indian performing arts.</li>
<li>Delicious Cuisine: The event will feature a variety of delicious Indian delicacies and beverages to keep participants energized throughout the evening. From mouth-watering chaats to aromatic biryanis and refreshing drinks, the food stalls will provide a delightful culinary experience.</li>
<li>Competitions and Prizes: Many prizes to win in this event.</li>
<li>Family-friendly Environment: The event is family-oriented, welcoming people of all ages to participate in the festivities. Special attention will be given to creating a safe and inclusive environment, ensuring that even children and the elderly can enjoy the event to the fullest</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Year Blast &#124; Greatest Evening Ever &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/new-year-blast-greatest-evening-ever-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curated menus with some great offers on food &#38; drinks, coupled with the best DJs bringing you beats till you drop. Plenty of good vibes all around, as everyone gets ready to bid goodbye to the year that was. Yes, there&#8217;s hardly a better way to greet 2024 than on the dance floor. But given &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/new-year-blast-greatest-evening-ever-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">New Year Blast &#124; Greatest Evening Ever &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curated menus with some great offers on food &amp; drinks, coupled with the best DJs bringing you beats till you drop. Plenty of good vibes all around, as everyone gets ready to bid goodbye to the year that was.</p>
<p>Yes, there&#8217;s hardly a better way to greet 2024 than on the dance floor. But given these times, there&#8217;s going to be limited entries this year. From clubs to 5-star hotels to open-air venues, you will find parties across budgets, all over the city.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holi Hai &#124; The Land of Colours @ Aqua Pune</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/holi-hai-the-land-of-colours-aqua-pune/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17241</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Get ready for the Most ‘Splashtastic Holi Bash in Pune’! Get drenched in fun &#38; excitement at Wet N Joy Splas. This Holi, Splash water in the “India’s Biggest Wave Pool Party” and get High on Non-stop Music. Get access to unlimited Rides, Wavepool, Rain Dance, Meals, Thandai &#38; Fun all day.. Enjoy 25 International &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/holi-hai-the-land-of-colours-aqua-pune/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Holi Hai &#124; The Land of Colours @ Aqua Pune</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Get ready for the Most ‘Splashtastic Holi Bash in Pune’! Get drenched in fun &amp; excitement at Wet N Joy Splas.</p>
<p>This Holi, Splash water in the “India’s Biggest Wave Pool Party” and get High on Non-stop Music. Get access to unlimited Rides, Wavepool, Rain Dance, Meals, Thandai &amp; Fun all day.. Enjoy 25 International Rides and Activities brought from North America &amp; Canada</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
