<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Myceremic Industries Ltd</title>
	<atom:link href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/mep_org/myceremic-industries-ltd/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 07:51:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/favicon-32x32-1.png</url>
	<title>Myceremic Industries Ltd</title>
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Raas Dandiya Fever &#124; Dandiya Nights &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/raas-dandiya-fever-dandiya-nights-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enchanting Rhythms: Dandiya Fever Festival is an exuberant and vibrant celebration of traditional Indian culture, specifically centered around the traditional folk dance form of Dandiya Raas. Colorful Costumes encouraged participants to wear in the event. DJ Music and Performances: Dandiya music, creating an energetic atmosphere that will keep participants dancing. Professional performers may also grace &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/raas-dandiya-fever-dandiya-nights-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Raas Dandiya Fever &#124; Dandiya Nights &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enchanting Rhythms: Dandiya Fever Festival is an exuberant and vibrant celebration of traditional Indian culture, specifically centered around the traditional folk dance form of Dandiya Raas.</p>
<ul>
<li>Colorful Costumes encouraged participants to wear in the event.</li>
<li>DJ Music and Performances: Dandiya music, creating an energetic atmosphere that will keep participants dancing. Professional performers may also grace the stage with captivating dance routines, showcasing the beauty and diversity of Indian performing arts.</li>
<li>Delicious Cuisine: The event will feature a variety of delicious Indian delicacies and beverages to keep participants energized throughout the evening. From mouth-watering chaats to aromatic biryanis and refreshing drinks, the food stalls will provide a delightful culinary experience.</li>
<li>Competitions and Prizes: Many prizes to win in this event.</li>
<li>Family-friendly Environment: The event is family-oriented, welcoming people of all ages to participate in the festivities. Special attention will be given to creating a safe and inclusive environment, ensuring that even children and the elderly can enjoy the event to the fullest</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bas Kar Bassi By Anubhav Bassi &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anubhav Singh Bassi is an Indian actor, YouTuber and stand-up comedian. His career as a standup comic started after an open mic in 2017. After the great success of his previous show &#8220;Bas kar bassi,&#8221; Anubhav Singh Bassi is coming back to perform live on stage. This time, he will bring a whole new set &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Bas Kar Bassi By Anubhav Bassi &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anubhav Singh Bassi is an Indian actor, YouTuber and stand-up comedian. His career as a standup comic started after an open mic in 2017.</p>
<p>After the great success of his previous show &#8220;Bas kar bassi,&#8221; Anubhav Singh Bassi is coming back to perform live on stage. This time, he will bring a whole new set of funny stories and jokes that will keep you entertained. Get ready to enjoy an exciting and hilarious performance that will make you laugh uncontrollably and leave you in high spirits.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Art &#038; Camp; Design Education Expo 2023 &#8211; Pune</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/global-art-design-education-expo-2023-pune/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[India&#8217;s biggest Art &#38; Design focused higher education fair organized by Zista Events Welcome to the 7th edition of the Global Art &#38; Design Education Expo; India’s biggest Art and Design focused higher education fair. It brings together the world’s leading creative institute, and students interested in the field of creative arts, design and technology. &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/global-art-design-education-expo-2023-pune/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Global Art &#38; Camp; Design Education Expo 2023 &#8211; Pune</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>India&#8217;s biggest Art &amp; Design focused higher education fair organized by Zista Events</strong></p>
<p>Welcome to the 7th edition of the Global Art &amp; Design Education Expo; India’s biggest Art and Design focused higher education fair. It brings together the world’s leading creative institute, and students interested in the field of creative arts, design and technology. Join us, and immerse yourself in an engaging, inspiring environment designed to shape the artists of tomorrow.</p>
<p><strong>Benefits to Students:</strong></p>
<p>• Get deeper insights into career opportunities in Art &amp; Design</p>
<p>• Meet expert representatives and academicians</p>
<p>• Attend thought-provoking breakout sessions and learn from panel discussions</p>
<p>• Meet like-minded peers and exchange ideas</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Classical Over Night Music Fest &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/classical-over-night-music-fest-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17244</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Mhatre Art Foundation is organising a classical music concert that will start with a recital by Gauri Pathare, a renowned vocalist known for her unique style. ecipient of Swarbhaskar award and Aditya Birla award, Gauri will be accompanied by Harshad Kanitkar on the tabla and Chaitnya Kunte on the harmonium for the performance. The evening &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/classical-over-night-music-fest-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Classical Over Night Music Fest &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mhatre Art Foundation is organising a classical music concert that will start with a recital by Gauri Pathare, a renowned vocalist known for her unique style. ecipient of Swarbhaskar award and Aditya Birla award, Gauri will be accompanied by Harshad Kanitkar on the tabla and Chaitnya Kunte on the harmonium for the performance.</p>
<p>The evening will conclude with a santoor recital by world renowned maestro, Pandit Satish Vyas. He will perform along with tabla player, Shri Ojas Adhiya.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Music Fest &#8211; Greatest Musical Night &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/music-fest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 20:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Music Fest is a community event with performances of singing and instrument playing that is often presented with a theme such as musical genre (e.g., rock, blues, folk, jazz, classical music), nationality, locality of musicians, or holiday. Music festivals are generally organized by individuals or organizations within networks of music production, typically music scenes, the music industries, or institutions of music education. The Sanremo Music Festival is the longest-running music festival &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/music-fest/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Music Fest &#8211; Greatest Musical Night &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A <b>Music Fest</b> is a community event with performances of singing and instrument playing that is often presented with a theme such as musical genre (e.g., rock, blues, folk, jazz, classical music), nationality, locality of musicians, or holiday. Music festivals are generally organized by individuals or organizations within networks of music production, typically music scenes, the music industries, or institutions of music education.</p>
<p>The Sanremo Music Festival is the longest-running music festival in the world<sup id="cite_ref-13" class="reference">, </sup> and it is also the basis and inspiration for the annual Eurovision Song Contest.<sup id="cite_ref-14" class="reference"></sup> Milwaukee, Wisconsin&#8217;s 11-day event, Summerfest, promotes itself as &#8220;The World&#8217;s Largest Music Festival.&#8221; Operating annually since 1968, the festival attracts between 800,000 and 1,000,000 people each year, and hosts over 800 musical acts.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
