<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin</title>
	<atom:link href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 09:39:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/favicon-32x32-1.png</url>
	<title>admin</title>
	<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dhaga &#124; Exotic Vintage Clothing &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/dhaga-exotic-vintage-clothing-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When it comes to fashion, visuals are key. It’s no wonder, then, that many lovers of style turn to Instagram and fashion blogs to get their fill of all things fashion. Instagram is great when it comes to OOTDs—outfit of the day—and quick style inspirations, but blogs are where the serious fashionistas go to write &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/dhaga-exotic-vintage-clothing-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Dhaga &#124; Exotic Vintage Clothing &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to fashion, visuals are key. It’s no wonder, then, that many lovers of style turn to Instagram and fashion blogs to get their fill of all things fashion. Instagram is great when it comes to OOTDs—outfit of the day—and quick style inspirations, but blogs are where the serious fashionistas go to write about trends, advice, and the latest fashion innovations.</p>
<p>The rise of fashionable Instagram influencers and stylists paved the way for the bloggers on our list to have a significant presence online. Many of these bloggers started out on social media, and their keen eye for style did not go unnoticed by their followers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kapil Sharma Comedy King &#124; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/kapil-sharma-comedy-king-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17493</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kapil Sharma is a renowned Indian comedian, actor, and television host. He gained popularity with his stand-up comedy acts and went on to host the hit comedy talk show &#8220;Comedy Nights with Kapil&#8221; and its successor &#8220;The Kapil Sharma Show.&#8221; Known for his impeccable timing and witty humor, Kapil Sharma has entertained audiences with his &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/kapil-sharma-comedy-king-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Kapil Sharma Comedy King &#124; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kapil Sharma is a renowned Indian comedian, actor, and television host. He gained popularity with his stand-up comedy acts and went on to host the hit comedy talk show &#8220;Comedy Nights with Kapil&#8221; and its successor &#8220;The Kapil Sharma Show.&#8221;</p>
<p>Known for his impeccable timing and witty humor, Kapil Sharma has entertained audiences with his unique style. He has also ventured into acting, appearing in Bollywood films such as &#8220;Kis Kisko Pyaar Karoon&#8221; and &#8220;Firangi.&#8221; With his charm and comic genius, Kapil Sharma has become one of the most loved and influential entertainers in India.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raas Dandiya Fever &#124; Dandiya Nights &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/raas-dandiya-fever-dandiya-nights-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17488</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enchanting Rhythms: Dandiya Fever Festival is an exuberant and vibrant celebration of traditional Indian culture, specifically centered around the traditional folk dance form of Dandiya Raas. Colorful Costumes encouraged participants to wear in the event. DJ Music and Performances: Dandiya music, creating an energetic atmosphere that will keep participants dancing. Professional performers may also grace &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/raas-dandiya-fever-dandiya-nights-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Raas Dandiya Fever &#124; Dandiya Nights &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enchanting Rhythms: Dandiya Fever Festival is an exuberant and vibrant celebration of traditional Indian culture, specifically centered around the traditional folk dance form of Dandiya Raas.</p>
<ul>
<li>Colorful Costumes encouraged participants to wear in the event.</li>
<li>DJ Music and Performances: Dandiya music, creating an energetic atmosphere that will keep participants dancing. Professional performers may also grace the stage with captivating dance routines, showcasing the beauty and diversity of Indian performing arts.</li>
<li>Delicious Cuisine: The event will feature a variety of delicious Indian delicacies and beverages to keep participants energized throughout the evening. From mouth-watering chaats to aromatic biryanis and refreshing drinks, the food stalls will provide a delightful culinary experience.</li>
<li>Competitions and Prizes: Many prizes to win in this event.</li>
<li>Family-friendly Environment: The event is family-oriented, welcoming people of all ages to participate in the festivities. Special attention will be given to creating a safe and inclusive environment, ensuring that even children and the elderly can enjoy the event to the fullest</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Year Blast &#124; Greatest Evening Ever &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/new-year-blast-greatest-evening-ever-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Curated menus with some great offers on food &#38; drinks, coupled with the best DJs bringing you beats till you drop. Plenty of good vibes all around, as everyone gets ready to bid goodbye to the year that was. Yes, there&#8217;s hardly a better way to greet 2024 than on the dance floor. But given &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/new-year-blast-greatest-evening-ever-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">New Year Blast &#124; Greatest Evening Ever &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Curated menus with some great offers on food &amp; drinks, coupled with the best DJs bringing you beats till you drop. Plenty of good vibes all around, as everyone gets ready to bid goodbye to the year that was.</p>
<p>Yes, there&#8217;s hardly a better way to greet 2024 than on the dance floor. But given these times, there&#8217;s going to be limited entries this year. From clubs to 5-star hotels to open-air venues, you will find parties across budgets, all over the city.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sensational Jubin Nautiyal Live Concert &#8211; Delhi 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/sensational-jubin-nautiyal-live-concert-delhi-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17479</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jubin Nautiyal is an Indian playback singer and live performer. In June 2022, he won the IIFA award for “Playback Singer ” for the song “Raataan Lambiyan.” He was awarded Upcoming Male Vocalist of the Year at 8th Mirchi Music Awards for his song &#8220;Zindagi Kuch Toh Bata&#8221; from Bajrangi Bhaijaan. Get ready to be &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/sensational-jubin-nautiyal-live-concert-delhi-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Sensational Jubin Nautiyal Live Concert &#8211; Delhi 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jubin Nautiyal is an Indian playback singer and live performer. In June 2022, he won the IIFA award for “Playback Singer ” for the song “Raataan Lambiyan.” He was awarded Upcoming Male Vocalist of the Year at 8th Mirchi Music Awards for his song &#8220;Zindagi Kuch Toh Bata&#8221; from Bajrangi Bhaijaan.</p>
<p>Get ready to be captivated by Jubin Nautiyal’s soulful voice and dynamic stage presence. Take advantage of discounted ticket prices for a limited time only. Join the jubilant crowd and immerse yourself in the magic of Jubin Nautiyal’s music.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Music Melodious &#8211; Shreya Ghoshal &#8211; Mumbai 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/music-melodious-shreya-ghoshal-mumbai-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 06:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17475</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Experience the melodious voice of Shreya Ghoshal by booking your tickets for her upcoming live shows. With the convenience of buying online tickets and a list of upcoming event dates available, you can easily plan your attendance to fit your schedule. Don’t miss out on the chance to see Shreya Ghoshal perform her greatest hits &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/music-melodious-shreya-ghoshal-mumbai-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Music Melodious &#8211; Shreya Ghoshal &#8211; Mumbai 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Experience the melodious voice of Shreya Ghoshal by booking your tickets for her upcoming live shows. With the convenience of buying online tickets and a list of upcoming event dates available, you can easily plan your attendance to fit your schedule. Don’t miss out on the chance to see Shreya Ghoshal perform her greatest hits and new material live on stage.</p>
<p>Shreya Ghoshal is indian playback singer. She is alos performed so many live show and concerts. She was seen by Sanjay Leela Bhansali when she won the musical Sa Re Ga Ma Pa at the sixteen years old.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kishor Da &#8211; The OG Superstar Musical Night &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/kishor-da-the-og-superstar-musical-night-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17271</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kishore Kumar (born Abhas Kumar Ganguly  4 August 1929 – 13 October 1987) was an Indian playback singer, musician and actor.  He is widely regarded as one of the greatest, most influential and dynamic singers in the history of Indian music. Kumar was one of the most popular singers in the Indian subcontinent, notable for his yodeling and ability to sing &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/kishor-da-the-og-superstar-musical-night-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Kishor Da &#8211; The OG Superstar Musical Night &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><b>Kishore Kumar</b> (born <b>Abhas Kumar Ganguly </b> 4 August 1929 – 13 October 1987) was an Indian playback singer, musician and actor.  He is widely regarded as one of the greatest, most influential and dynamic singers in the history of Indian music. Kumar was one of the most popular singers in the Indian subcontinent, notable for his yodeling and ability to sing songs in different voices.  He used to sing in different genres but some of his rare compositions, considered classics, were lost in time.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Zakir Khan Show &#8211; Pune  2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Zakir Khan is one of the the brightest comedians in the country, as proven by the massive success of his recent Haq Se Single tour, and the Amazon Prime special of the same name. Zakir created waves in 2016 with his appearance on AIB Diwas, as he swiftly went on to become what AIB founder &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023-2/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The Zakir Khan Show &#8211; Pune  2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zakir Khan is one of the the brightest comedians in the country, as proven by the massive success of his recent Haq Se Single tour, and the Amazon Prime special of the same name. Zakir created waves in 2016 with his appearance on AIB Diwas, as he swiftly went on to become what AIB founder Tanmay Bhat described as “The biggest stand-up comedy act in India. Period”.</p>
<p>A writer by profession, this &#8216;Confused Desi&#8217; serves his take on modern India, with a hard-to-resist style of humour that&#8217;ll have you nodding your heads and clapping as you relate to everything he says.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bas Kar Bassi By Anubhav Bassi &#8211; Pune 2023</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anubhav Singh Bassi is an Indian actor, YouTuber and stand-up comedian. His career as a standup comic started after an open mic in 2017. After the great success of his previous show &#8220;Bas kar bassi,&#8221; Anubhav Singh Bassi is coming back to perform live on stage. This time, he will bring a whole new set &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/the-zakir-khan-show-pune-2023/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Bas Kar Bassi By Anubhav Bassi &#8211; Pune 2023</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anubhav Singh Bassi is an Indian actor, YouTuber and stand-up comedian. His career as a standup comic started after an open mic in 2017.</p>
<p>After the great success of his previous show &#8220;Bas kar bassi,&#8221; Anubhav Singh Bassi is coming back to perform live on stage. This time, he will bring a whole new set of funny stories and jokes that will keep you entertained. Get ready to enjoy an exciting and hilarious performance that will make you laugh uncontrollably and leave you in high spirits.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Art &#038; Camp; Design Education Expo 2023 &#8211; Pune</title>
		<link>https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/global-art-design-education-expo-2023-pune/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 06:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/?post_type=mep_events#038;p=17249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[India&#8217;s biggest Art &#38; Design focused higher education fair organized by Zista Events Welcome to the 7th edition of the Global Art &#38; Design Education Expo; India’s biggest Art and Design focused higher education fair. It brings together the world’s leading creative institute, and students interested in the field of creative arts, design and technology. &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://vinnie1818.github.io/eventlistener/event/global-art-design-education-expo-2023-pune/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Global Art &#38; Camp; Design Education Expo 2023 &#8211; Pune</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>India&#8217;s biggest Art &amp; Design focused higher education fair organized by Zista Events</strong></p>
<p>Welcome to the 7th edition of the Global Art &amp; Design Education Expo; India’s biggest Art and Design focused higher education fair. It brings together the world’s leading creative institute, and students interested in the field of creative arts, design and technology. Join us, and immerse yourself in an engaging, inspiring environment designed to shape the artists of tomorrow.</p>
<p><strong>Benefits to Students:</strong></p>
<p>• Get deeper insights into career opportunities in Art &amp; Design</p>
<p>• Meet expert representatives and academicians</p>
<p>• Attend thought-provoking breakout sessions and learn from panel discussions</p>
<p>• Meet like-minded peers and exchange ideas</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
